See this picture
It is a round button
Then there are two holes in the middle
What about this kind of button
There is one in CLO
We see the window of this picture book
Subtract
Here I will switch to the list display
Find the button and the button eye file
Open the button
In these buttons
Find two round buttons that meet our needs
Switch to display icon
Convenient for us to look at the search chart
Just like this
The mouse stops on the button and a number appears
A line button 9
Remember this number
Then go up
Find the Uv document folder
Double click to open
In any document
Right click on the document
Copy the path
Open the file
Then paste and return to the path
There are many PSD files here
These are the standard files that CLO has prepared for you
We just need to follow the tips
You can do the uv picture step by step
Open PS
A line button 9
Drag to PS to open
After opening, we can see the drawing
According to this color, several areas are divided
And there is a corresponding text on it to remind
The biggest one on the top is the front of the button
The bottom is the back
The upper right corner is the side of the button eye
Because it is two buttons
So there are two small lines here
The text is in Chinese, English and Korean
We can only keep Chinese
On the right layer here
Hide the other two words
Just show Chinese
Drag the button drawing in
Use the mouse left key
The mouse left key can be dragged directly
Put it on the back here first
Pull the empty square of the school
Can be magnified
Zoom in and take a look
Put the picture next to it
Take a closer look
We have to ensure that this twisted picture
It can cover the bottom
This green circle
Can be a little bigger
Basically covered
Then click on this hook above
Right click on the layer
Blur layer
Take off the good button
The eyes of these two lines are vertical
Choose the layer
Press CTRL plus K
At this time, you can adjust the size, shape, angle, etc.
Turn it to a vertical state
Then click on this hook above
We still need to take care of the eyes of the two lines
Because the size and position of these two eyes
In fact, the two eyes of the bottom board
It doesn't necessarily match
So in order to ensure
Don't make a difference in the twist texture
We need to take care of these two eyes
Turn it off
Turn it into
Vertical texture around
Use the set tool
Turn it up
At this time, a selection is generated
Fill in other patterns for this selection
The shortcut key is Shift plus F
Select content, identify content, confirm
Repeat the previous operation once more
Shift plus F
Then select the content to identify
Confirm
It will be handled soon
Copy the twist texture to one
CRTL plus C, CRTL plus V
Not yet
Here I want to remind everyone
Although this place only shows a front
But in fact this area
Its texture is except the front
There is also a circle is the side texture of this twist
A little magnification
This place has several circles
This white line
The white line on the outside
To the middle of the green line
This section of the range
Is the side texture of the twist
Pull the twist texture over
If the texture is not big enough
Let's adjust it again
Still CRTL plus T
A little bit bigger
Then cooperate with the direction key on the keyboard
Make a slight move
Click to match the direction key on the keyboard
Click the button to match
After putting the number
Let's do the side texture
The side of the twist is pure white
Make a big circle directly
Just fill the circle with white
Select the twist texture
Copy a CRTL plus J
Put this layer down
Still use CTRL plus T to pull the circle
Can be slightly larger than the green circle
Click to confirm
Press the CRTL key at the same time
Left mouse button
Press the layer to shrink
Then press Shift plus F5
Select white
CTRL plus D to cancel the selection
Next to deal with the side of the twist
Switch to the square selection tool
All the squares on the side of the twist are selected
Shift plus F5 fill in white
That's it
Then it will be a JPG picture
Before saving, you can hide other layers
Select the save address
Select the JPG format
According to the quality you need to choose
Here the selection is the highest level
Finally, click to confirm
Back to the software
Next, on this style
Use our new twist
Add a twist
Wait a moment
Then in the shape here
Find the two-eyed round twist we chose at the beginning
Continue to look down
There is a text here
There is a corresponding browser button next to it
Click to add the picture just now to it
Wait a moment
I still can't see the twist effect
You need to add the twist to this dress first
Switch to the move twist tool
Select all five twists in the front
Press Shift can choose more
Find the application button on the right side of the new twist
You can see the effect at the 3D window
This twist should be
The purple part is above
The white part is below
That is to say
The twist should rotate 90 degrees counterclockwise
Select all twists
There is a angle here in the property editor
Change to 90
Complete